A Guide to the Robert Whitehead Papers,
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Robert Whitehead Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
6409
This collection consists of items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Contents List
- 1
  - Papers re: Apple Industry 1943-1954 (Box-folder 1:1)
  - Clippings re: General Assembly 1952 (Box-folder 1:2)
  - General Assembly 1956 (Box-folder 1:3)
  - General Assembly 1958 (Box-folder 1:4)
  - High School Athletics 1959, Oct. (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Brookville High School Commencement Address 1958, June 6 (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Caucus System 1952, January (Box-folder 1:7)
  - Chesnut March 12, 1946-1955, Feb. 21 (Box-folder 1:8)
  - Constitution of Virginia (Box-folder 1:9)
  - Crabtree Falls re: Area proposed as a Federal Park 1939, May 4-1958, Sept. 9 (Box-folder 1:10)
  - Debt 1951-1955 (Box-folder 1:11)
  - Education 1950-51, 1952, 1953 (Box-folder 1:12)
  - Education 1954 (Box-folder 2:1)
  - Education 1954 (Box-folder 2:2)
  - Education 1955 (Box-folder 2:3)
  - Education re. Standing Legislation 1958 (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Education (1958 Session) See Finances 1958, 59, 60 (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Education (1958 Session) See Finances 1959, 1960 (Box-folder 2:6)
  - Elections (#2) 1949-1951 (Box-folder 2:7)
    a. 1949 Constitutional amendment
    b. See poll tax
  - Same as above (#1) 1949-1951 (Box-folder 2:8)
  - Election 1952-1954 (Box-folder 3:1)
  - Election 1953-1954 (Box-folder 3:2)
  - Election 1958-59 (Box-folder 3:3)
  - Election 1950 (Box-folder 3:4)
  - Alcoholics 1951-1958 (Box-folder 3:5)
  - Amherst County 1957-1960 (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Employees in Virginia 1941-1958 (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Finances for State of Virginia 1950-1951 (Box-folder 4:1)
  - Finance in Education, appropriations, budget. 1950-1952 (Box-folder 4:2)
  - Finances 1958 (Box-folder 4:3)
  - Extra finances 1958 (Box-folder 4:4)
  - Finances 1956 (Box-folder 4:5)
  - State Finances 1955 (Box-folder 5:1)
  - Finances re. Education 1957-1958 (Box-folder 5:2)
  - Game & Inland Fisheries 1957-59 (Box-folder 5:3)
  - Forestry 1958, March (Box-folder 5:4)
  - Fraternities; close at Wm. & Mary, & others 1942 (Box-folder 5:5)
  - Game 1958 (Box-folder 5:6)
  - Miscellaneous: Education, State of Va. (Box-folder 5:7)
  - Higher Education in Va. 1953-1955 (Box-folder 6:1)
  - Higher Education in Va. 1960 (Box-folder 6:2)
  - Hospital & Health in Va. 1948-1952 (Box-folder 6:3)
  - Industrialization in Va. 1959, July (Box-folder 6:4)
  - Labor in Va. 1954 (Box-folder 6:5)
  - Labor 1950, 1958, 1959 (Box-folder 6:6)
  - Labor Addresses 1952-1956 (Box-folder 6:7)
  - Bar Examination in Va. 1951-52 (Box-folder 6:8)
  - Lynchburg Training School & Hospital 1957-1960 (Box-folder 7:1)
  - Mawyer H. D. re. Voting 1959 (Box-folder 7:2)
  - Mental Hospitals re. Investigation, etc. 1956-1958 (Box-folder 7:3)
  - Mental Hospitals re. Adequate Appropriations 1950-1953 (Box-folder 7:4)
  - Tuck's Anti-Truman Bill 1948 (Box-folder 8:1)
  - Negro-Richmond Voting 1951-1952 (Box-folder 8:2)
  - Men's Club 1939 (Box-folder 8:3)
  - Milk 1957-1960 (Box-folder 8:4)
  - Public Affairs (Miscellaneous) 1933-1950 (Box-folder 8:5)
  - F. P. Miller 1949 (Box-folder 8:6)
  - Cattle Investigation 1956, June 21 (Box-folder 8:7)
  - Redistricting 1951-1952 (Box-folder 9:1)
  - Democratic Party, Presidential Election 1948 (Box-folder 9:2)
  - Pamphlets on Byrd Machine 1952 (Box-folder 9:3)
  - Negro Suffrage 1954-1956 (Box-folder 10:1)
  - Negro Suffrage 1953-1955 (Box-folder 10:2)
  - New Market Battlefield 1952 (Box-folder 10:3)
  - News Paper Clippings Miscellaneous 1948 (Box-folder 10:4)
  - Norfolk Address -1955, Jan. 29- (Box-folder 10:5)
  - Politics 1951 (Box-folder 10:6)
  - Poll Tax 1944-1951 (Box-folder 10:7)
  - Primary Election Laws 1951-1954 (Box-folder 10:8)
  - Public Affairs in Va. 1935-1955 (Box-folder 10:9)
  - House of Delegates Re-election for 1957 1957 (Box-folder 11:1)
  - Nelson Co. Servicemen Voting League 1944 (Box-folder 11:2)
  - Election Voting List 1947-1952 (Box-folder 11:3)
  - Byrd Machine 1957-1959 (Box-folder 11:4)
  - Bedford Chamber of Commerce 1955 (Box-folder 11:5)
  - Harry F. Byrd, Jr. - Taxes 1953, 54, 60 (Box-folder 11:6)
  - Robert Whitehead 1959 (Box-folder 11:7)
  - Democratic Committees 1943-1959 (Box-folder 11:8)
  - Democratic Club of Va. 1957-1960 (Box-folder 11:9)
  - Almond, Byrd, Tuck, Eisenhower 1957 (Box-folder 12:1)
  - Democrat Election 1957 1957 (Box-folder 12:2)
  - Democratic Convention, Harrisonburg Sept. 5, 1932 (Box-folder 12:3)
  - Democratic Party Matters 1940-1941 (Box-folder 12:4)
  - Democratic Party: Presidential & Congressional Elections 1944 (Box-folder 12:5)
  - Democratic Party 1946-47 (Box-folder 12:6)
  - Francis P. Miller 1952 (Box-folder 13:1)
  - Harry F. Byrd, Senate 1952 (Box-folder 13:2)
  - Francis P. Miller Re. Senate Race 1952 (Box-folder 13:3)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings re. Senatorial Campaign 1952 (Box-folder 13:4)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlet on Public Utilities 1951, Mar. 1 (Box-folder 13:5)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper 1957, July 20 (Box-folder 13:6)
  - Miller-Byrd 1952 Senate Race 1952 (Box-folder 14:1)
  - Democratic Primary (1949) Speeches 1949 (Box-folder 14:2)
  - Democratic Party 1951-52 (Box-folder 14:3)
  - 1953 Democratic Party Election re. Stanley vs. Dalton 1953 (Box-folder 14:4)
  - Democratic Party Affairs (1954 Elections) 1954 (Box-folder 14:5)
  - Democratic Party 1955-56 (Box-folder 14:6)
  - Democratic Party 1956-1957 (Box-folder 15:1)
  - Democratic Party 1956 Election 1956 (Box-folder 15:2)
  - Democratic Nominees to State Convention 1960 (Box-folder 15:3)
  - Democratic Committee Lists 1951 (Box-folder 15:4)
  - Elections 1935 (Box-folder 15:5)
  - Election Districts 1940, 1947 (Box-folder 15:6)
  - Election Returns 1911-1959 (Box-folder 15:7)
  - Election Returns State & National 1944-1959 (Box-folder 15:8)
  - Election Laws & Form 1951 (Box-folder 15:9)
  - Garnet Ewing 1948, 1949, 1957 (Box-folder 16:1)
  - Fairfax County Democrats Address 1955 (Box-folder 16:2)
  - Men's Club Industrial Committee 1950-1953 (Box-folder 16:3)
  - Carroll County Farm Address April 7, 1955 (Box-folder 16:4)
  - Farmers Union 1953-59 (Box-folder 16:5)
  - Farmers Union 1955-59 (Box-folder 16:6)
  - State Fire Chief's Association of Va. 1952 (Box-folder 17:1)
  - Democratic Party Affairs 1949-1950 (Box-folder 17:2)
  - Democratic Convention 1952 (Box-folder 17:3)
  - "Freedom of the Mind of Man" 1953-1955 (Box-folder 17:4)
  - Industrialization 1951 (Box-folder 17:5)
  - Public Addresses 1943-1950 (Box-folder 17:6)
  - Public Addresses 1951-1953 (Box-folder 17:7)
  - Public Addresses 1954-1960 (Box-folder 18:1)
  - Education 1955 (Box-folder 18:2)
  - Public Affairs 1937-1940 (Box-folder 18:3)
  - Redistricting 1958 (Box-folder 18:4)
  - Richmond Address 1955, April 15 (Box-folder 18:5)
  - Public & Political Education 1955 (Box-folder 18:6)
  - Roads & Road Taxes 1954-1957 (Box-folder 18:7)
  - Taxation 1947 (Box-folder 19:1)
  - Taxation (Money, Tobacco, Education) 1948 (Box-folder 19:2)
  - Newspapers on Taxation 1949 (Box-folder 19:3)
  - Taxation in Va. 1949-1951 (Box-folder 19:4)
  - Roads 1958-59 (Box-folder 19:5)
  - Roads 1960 (Box-folder 19:6)
  - Soil Conservation 1956, 57 (Box-folder 20:1)
  - State Corporation Commission 1941 & 1957 (Box-folder 20:2)
  - Taxation 1956-1957 (Box-folder 20:3)
  - Perrow Commission (Education) Segregation 1959 (Box-folder 20:4)
  - Summary of 1959 Session 1959 (Box-folder 20:5)
  - Editorials re. Perrow Comm. 1959 (Box-folder 20:6)
  - Report of Perrow Commission 1959 (Box-folder 20:7)
  - Byrd Automatic Tax Reduction Act 1952-1953 (Box-folder 20:8)
  - Byrd Tax Law & Finances 1954 (Box-folder 21:1)
  - Taxation 1954-1956 (Box-folder 21:2)
  - Amherst-Nelson Tournament Association 1952 (Box-folder 21:3)
  - Virginia Travel Council 1954-1955 (Box-folder 21:4)
  - Tuberculosis 1959 (Box-folder 21:5)
  - Va. Education Association 1958 (Box-folder 21:6)
  - Virginia's Government & Socialism 1952 (Box-folder 21:7)
  - War Memorial 1953-1954 (Box-folder 21:8)
  - Whitehead Newspaper Editorials Gubernatorial Race (Box-folder 21:9)
  - Robert Whitehead re. Newspaper Editorial Comments 1950-1957 (Box-folder 22:1)
  - Sallie C. Whitehead 1952-1953 (Box-folder 22:2)
  - Fraternities, etc. 1952-1955 (Box-folder 22:3)
  - Women in Virginia Civic Life 1951-1955 (Box-folder 22:4)
  - Y.M.C.A. 1952 (Box-folder 22:5)
  - Remarks made by Whitehead 1955 (Box-folder 22:6)
  - Nelson Co. & Amherst Co. local matter 1954-1956 (Box-folder 23:1)
  - Education: Perrow & Whitehead 1959 (Box-folder 23:2)
  - Whitehead supports Almond 1959 (Box-folder 23:3)
  - Whitehead Address in Charlottesville & Education 1959 (Box-folder 23:4)
  - Committee on Surplus Property 1959 (Box-folder 23:5)
  - Local Budgets: Perrow Commission & Murphy Commission 1959 (Box-folder 23:6)
  - Prince Edward County 1960 (Box-folder 23:7)
  - Pupil Placement; Perrow Comm. 1959 (Box-folder 23:8)
  - Pupil Placement 1960 (Box-folder 23:9)
  - Tuition Grants re. Perrow Commission & Button Comm. 1958-1959 (Box-folder 23:10)
  - Tuition Grants 1960 Session 1960 (Box-folder 23:11)
  - Bill of Rights Crusade 1959, April 14 (Box-folder 24:1)
  - Negro Education re. Leon Dure Plan 1959-1960 (Box-folder 24:2)
  - Amendment to Constit. of Va. re. Perrow Comm. 1959 (Box-folder 24:3)
  - Articles re. Perrow Comm. 1959 (Box-folder 24:4)
  - W. Taylor Murphy 1959 (Box-folder 24:5)
  - Interposition 1955-1956 (Box-folder 24:6)
  - Interposition #2 1956 (Box-folder 24:7)
  - Interposition re. Address of 1956, Feb. 1 (Box-folder 25:1)
  - Interposition #3 1956 (Box-folder 25:2)
  - Interposition re. Newspapers, etc. 1956 (Box-folder 25:3)
  - Civil Rights 1957 (Box-folder 25:4)
  - Negro Education re. Whitehead 1956-1959 (Box-folder 25:5)
  - Editorials 1959 (Box-folder 26:1)
  - Attorney General Harrison v. Day Comptroller 1958-1959 (Box-folder 26:2)
  - Negro Education 1959 (Box-folder 26:3)
  - Sit downs 1960 (Box-folder 26:4)
  - Negro Education re. Pamphlets, Circulars & Addresses 1955-1959 (Box-folder 26:5)
  - Negro Education re. Court Decisions 1955-1958 (Box-folder 26:6)
  - Negro Education re. Va. & North Carolina 1958-1959 (Box-folder 27:1)
  - Norfolk re. Elections 1959 (Box-folder 27:2)
  - Editorials #1 1949-1956 (Box-folder 27:3)
  - Editorials #1 1957-1958 (Box-folder 27:4)
  - Negro Education 1942-1953 (Box-folder 27:5)
  - Negro Education #2 1954 (Box-folder 27:6)
  - Negro Education #3 1954 (Box-folder 28:1)
  - Negro Education #4 1955 (Box-folder 28:2)
  - Negro Education #5 1955 (Box-folder 28:3)
  - Negro Education #6 1955-1956 (Box-folder 28:4)
  - Negro Education #7 1956 (Box-folder 28:5)
  - Negro Education #8 1956 (Box-folder 29:1)
  - Negro Education #9 1956 (Box-folder 29:2)
  - Negro Education #10 1956 (Box-folder 29:3)
  - Negro Education #11 1956 (Box-folder 29:4)
  - Negro Education #12 1956-1957 (Box-folder 29:5)
  - Negro Education #13 1958 (Box-folder 29:6)
  - Negro Education #14 1958 (Box-folder 30:1)
  - Negro Education #15 1959 (Box-folder 30:2)
  - Negro Education McCue's Plan for Va. schools 1956 (Box-folder 30:3)
  - Moore Resolution re. Negro Education 1954-1956 (Box-folder 30:4)
  - Tobacco Tax 1953-1960 (Box-folder 30:5)
  - Miscellaneous Newspapers 1960 (Box-folder 30:6)
  - Finances 1960 #1 1960 (Box-folder 31:1)
  - Finances 1960 #2 1960 (Box-folder 31:2)
  - Whiskey, Wine, & Beer Taxation 1960 (Box-folder 31:3)
  - Democratic "Straight Ticket Committee" 1960 (Box-folder 31:4)
  - Retirement in Virginia 1960 (Box-folder 31:5)
  - Politics 1960 (Box-folder 31:6)
  - Miscellaneous Letters re. Whitehead 1960 (Box-folder 31:7)
- 2
  - Miscellaneous re. Membership of House of Delegates 1942 (Box-folder 1:1)
  - Agriculture 1942 (Box-folder 1:2)
  - A 1942 (Box-folder 1:3)
  - B 1942 (Box-folder 1:4)
  - C 1942 (Box-folder 1:5)
  - D 1942 (Box-folder 1:6)
  - E-F 1942 (Box-folder 1:7)
  - G 1942 (Box-folder 1:8)
  - H-I-J 1942 (Box-folder 1:9)
  - K-L 1942 (Box-folder 1:10)
  - M 1942 (Box-folder 1:11)
  - N-O 1942 (Box-folder 1:12)
  - P-Q 1942 (Box-folder 1:13)
  - R 1942 (Box-folder 1:14)
  - S 1942 (Box-folder 1:15)
  - Workmen's Compensation 1941 (Box-folder 1:16)
  - W 1941 (Box-folder 1:17)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1941 (Box-folder 1:18)
  - ABC Matters 1942 (Box-folder 2:1)
    (Whitehead Member House of Delegates 1942 Session)
  - Education 1942 (Box-folder 2:2)
  - Miscellanea 1942 (Box-folder 2:3)
  - A 1942 (Box-folder 2:4)
  - B 1942 (Box-folder 2:5)
  - C 1942 (Box-folder 2:6)
  - D 1942 (Box-folder 2:7)
  - E-F 1942 (Box-folder 2:8)
  - G 1942 (Box-folder 2:9)
  - H-I-J 1942 (Box-folder 2:10)
  - K-L 1942 (Box-folder 2:11)
  - M 1942 (Box-folder 2:12)
  - Motor Vehicles 1942 (Box-folder 2:13)
  - N-O 1942 (Box-folder 2:14)
  - Redistricting 1942 (Box-folder 2:15)
  - Schools 1942 (Box-folder 2:16)
  - Schools 1942 (Box-folder 2:17)
  - S 1942 (Box-folder 2:18)
  - T-U-V 1942 (Box-folder 2:19)
  - W 1942 (Box-folder 2:20)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1942 (Box-folder 2:21)
  - Announcing of Candidacy 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:1)
    (Whitehead, House of Delegates, from close of 1942 Session to December 31, 1943)
  - Miscellanea 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:2)
  - A 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:3)
  - B 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:4)
  - C 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:5)
  - D 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:6)
  - E-F 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:7)
  - G 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:8)
  - H-I-J 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:9)
  - K-L 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:10)
  - M 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:11)
  - N-O 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:12)
  - P-Q 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:13)
  - R 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:14)
  - S 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:15)
  - T-U-V 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:16)
  - W 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:17)
  - Y-Z 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:18)
  - Letters of praise after first session of General Assembly 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3:19)
  - Bills of Robert Whitehead 1944 (Box-folder 4:1)
    (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1944, Jan. 1-1944, Mar. 31)
  - A 1944 (Box-folder 4:2)
  - Bonus Bill for State Employees 1944 (Box-folder 4:3)
  - B 1944 (Box-folder 4:4)
  - C 1944 (Box-folder 4:5)
  - D 1944 (Box-folder 4:6)
  - Forest Fire Control 1944 (Box-folder 4:7)
  - E-F 1944 (Box-folder 4:8)
  - G 1944 (Box-folder 4:9)
  - H-I-J 1944 (Box-folder 4:10)
  - K-L 1944 (Box-folder 4:11)
  - M 1944 (Box-folder 4:12)
  - N-O 1944 (Box-folder 4:13)
  - P-Q 1944 (Box-folder 4:14)
  - R 1944 (Box-folder 4:15)
  - S 1944 (Box-folder 4:16)
  - Small Loan Legislation 1944 (Box-folder 4:17)
  - T-U-V 1944 (Box-folder 4:18)
  - W 1944 (Box-folder 4:19)
  - J. Roy Woodson 1944 (Box-folder 4:20)
  - Comptroller's Reports 1944 (Box-folder 4a:1)
    [Education & Related Fiscal Matters only]
  - Education #1 1944 (Box-folder 4a:2)
  - Education #2 1944 (Box-folder 4a:3)
  - A 1944 (Box-folder 4a:4)
  - B 1944 (Box-folder 4a:5)
    [Education & Related Fiscal Mattersonly]
  - C 1944 (Box-folder 4a:6)
  - D 1944 (Box-folder 4a:7)
  - E-F 1944 (Box-folder 4a:8)
  - G-H-I-J 1944 (Box-folder 4a:9)
  - K-L 1944 (Box-folder 4a:10)
  - M-N-O 1944 (Box-folder 4a:11)
  - P-Q-R-S 1944 (Box-folder 4a:12)
  - T-U-V-W-X-Y-Z 1944 (Box-folder 4a:13)
  - Education #3; Newspaper Clippings 1944 (Box-folder 4a:14)
  - Miscellaneous 1944 (Box-folder 5:1)
    (April 1, 1944 to December 31, 1944)
  - A 1944 (Box-folder 5:2)
  - B 1944 (Box-folder 5:3)
  - C 1944 (Box-folder 5:4)
  - D 1944 (Box-folder 5:5)
  - E-F 1944 (Box-folder 5:6)
  - G 1944 (Box-folder 5:7)
  - H-I-J 1944 (Box-folder 5:8)
  - K-L 1944 (Box-folder 5:9)
  - M 1944 (Box-folder 5:10)
  - N-O 1944 (Box-folder 5:11)
  - P-Q 1944 (Box-folder 5:12)
  - R 1944 (Box-folder 5:13)
  - Surplus Federal Property 1944 (Box-folder 5:14)
  - Soldier Vote Matters 1944 (Box-folder 5:15)
  - S 1944 (Box-folder 5:16)
  - T-U-V 1944 (Box-folder 5:17)
  - W-Y-Z 1944 (Box-folder 5:18)
  - Miscellaneous 1944 (Box-folder 5:19)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - Education (Box-folder 6:1)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - A (Box-folder 6:2)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - B (Box-folder 6:3)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - Carney, Judge A.B. (Box-folder 6:4)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - C (Box-folder 6:5)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - D (Box-folder 6:6)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - E-F (Box-folder 6:7)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - G (Box-folder 6:8)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - H-I-J (Box-folder 6:9)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - K-L (Box-folder 6:10)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - Muse, Leonard G. (Box-folder 6:11)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - M-N-O (Box-folder 6:12)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - Poll Tax Refund (Box-folder 6:13)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - P-Q-R (Box-folder 6:14)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - S (Box-folder 6:15)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - T-U-V (Box-folder 6:16)
  - (Whitehead in House of Delegates from 1945, Jan. 1-1945, Dec. 31) - W-Z (Box-folder 6:17)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - Amherst County Park (Box-folder 7:1)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - Telephones 1946 File & 1948 File (Box-folder 7:2)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - A (Box-folder 7:3)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - B (Box-folder 7:4)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - C (Box-folder 7:5)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - D-E-F (Box-folder 7:6)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - G (Box-folder 7:7)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - Health & Related Matters (Box-folder 7:8)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - H-I-J (Box-folder 7:9)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - Historical Markers (Box-folder 7:10)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - Labor & Industry 1946 (Box-folder 7:11)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - K-L (Box-folder 7:12)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - M (Box-folder 7:13)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - N-O (Box-folder 7:14)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - P-Q (Box-folder 7:15)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - R (Box-folder 7:16)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - S (Box-folder 7:17)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - T-U-V (Box-folder 7:18)
  - [Whitehead-House of Delegates from 1946, Jan. 1-July 31.] - W (Box-folder 7:19)
  - [Whitehead; re. Education, Finances, Roads Taxation 1946, Jan. 1 - Dec. 31] - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 7a:1)
  - [Whitehead; re. Education, Finances, Roads Taxation 1946, Jan. 1 - Dec. 31] - Education - 1946 (Box-folder 7a:2)
  - [Whitehead; re. Education, Finances, Roads Taxation 1946, Jan. 1 - Dec. 31] - Finances - 1946 (Box-folder 7a:3)
  - [Whitehead; re. Education, Finances, Roads Taxation 1946, Jan. 1 - Dec. 31] - Free Textbooks - 1946 & 1947 (Box-folder 7a:4)
  - [Whitehead; re. Education, Finances, Roads Taxation 1946, Jan. 1 - Dec. 31] - Roads 1946 Session (Box-folder 7a:5)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 8:1)
  - A (Box-folder 8:2)
  - B (Box-folder 8:3)
  - C (Box-folder 8:4)
  - D (Box-folder 8:5)
  - E-F (Box-folder 8:6)
  - G (Box-folder 8:7)
  - H-I-J (Box-folder 8:8)
  - K-L (Box-folder 8:9)
  - M (Box-folder 8:10)
  - N-O-P-Q (Box-folder 8:11)
  - R (Box-folder 8:12)
  - S (Box-folder 8:13)
  - T-U-V (Box-folder 8:14)
  - W-Z (Box-folder 8:15)
  - 1947 (Box-folder 8a:1)
    [Whitehead-House of Delegates: Education, Finances, Taxation, 1947 Jan. 1 - Dec. 31]
  - Taxation 1946 Session (Box-folder 8a:2)
  - Finance & Education 1947 Special Session (Box-folder 8a:3)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 8a:4)
  - A (Box-folder 8a:5)
  - B-C-D (Box-folder 8a:6)
  - G-M (Box-folder 8a:7)
  - N-Z (Box-folder 8a:8)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 8a:9)
  - A (Box-folder 9:1)
    [Whitehead - House of Delegates 1948 Jan. 1 - March 31]
  - B (Box-folder 9:2)
  - C (Box-folder 9:3)
  - D-E-F (Box-folder 9:4)
  - James River Road - Madison Heights to Scottsville (Box-folder 9:5)
  - Health (Box-folder 9:6)
  - H-I-J (Box-folder 9:7)
  - K-L (Box-folder 9:8)
  - M (Box-folder 9:9)
  - N-Q (Box-folder 9:10)
  - R (Box-folder 9:11)
  - S (Box-folder 9:12)
  - W-Z (Box-folder 9:13)
  - Elections 1946 File & 1948 File (Box-folder 9a:1)
    [Whitehead, House of Delegates, 1948, Jan. 1-March 31]
  - A-C (Box-folder 9a:2)
  - D-F (Box-folder 9a:3)
  - Education - 1948 (Box-folder 9a:4)
  - G-M (Box-folder 9a:5)
  - N-Q (Box-folder 9a:6)
  - Roads - 1948 see 1946 File (Box-folder 9a:7)
  - R-Z (Box-folder 9a:8)
  - A (Box-folder 10:1)
    [Whitehead, House of Delegates, 1948 April 1-1949 Dec. 31]
  - B (Box-folder 10:2)
  - C (Box-folder 10:3)
  - D (Box-folder 10:4)
  - E-F (Box-folder 10:5)
  - G (Box-folder 10:6)
  - H-I-J (Box-folder 10:7)
  - K-L (Box-folder 10:8)
  - M (Box-folder 10:9)
  - N-O (Box-folder 10:10)
  - P-Q (Box-folder 10:11)
  - R (Box-folder 10:12)
  - S (Box-folder 10:13)
  - T-U-V (Box-folder 10:14)
  - W-Z (Box-folder 10:15)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 10:16)
  - A (Box-folder 11:1)
    [Whitehead, House of Delegates, 1950 Jan. 1-1951, Dec. 31]
  - B (Box-folder 11:2)
  - C (Box-folder 11:3)
  - D (Box-folder 11:4)
  - E-F (Box-folder 11:5)
  - G (Box-folder 11:6)
  - H-I-J (Box-folder 11:7)
  - K-L (Box-folder 11:8)
  - M (Box-folder 11:9)
  - N-O (Box-folder 11:10)
  - P-Q (Box-folder 11:11)
  - R (Box-folder 11:12)
  - S (Box-folder 11:13)
  - M (Box-folder 15:11)
  - N-O (Box-folder 15:12)
  - P-Q (Box-folder 15:13)
  - R (Box-folder 15:14)
  - S (Box-folder 15:15)
  - T-U-V (Box-folder 15:16)
  - W-Z (Box-folder 15:17)
  - A (Box-folder 16:1)
    [Whitehead, House of Delegates, 1954, Jan. 1-1955, Dec. 31]
  - B (Box-folder 16:2)
  - C (Box-folder 16:3)
  - D (Box-folder 16:4)
  - E-F (Box-folder 16:5)
  - G (Box-folder 16:6)
  - H-I-J (Box-folder 16:7)
  - K-L (Box-folder 16:8)
  - M (Box-folder 16:9)
  - N-O (Box-folder 16:10)
  - P-Q (Box-folder 16:11)
  - R (Box-folder 16:12)
  - S (Box-folder 16:13)
  - T-U-V (Box-folder 16:14)
  - W-Z (Box-folder 16:15)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 17:1)
    [Whitehead, House of Delegates, 1956, Jan. 1-Dec. 31]
  - A (Box-folder 17:2)
  - B (Box-folder 17:3)
  - C (Box-folder 17:4)
  - D (Box-folder 17:5)
  - E-F (Box-folder 17:6)
  - G-J (Box-folder 17:7)
  - K-L (Box-folder 17:8)
  - M (Box-folder 17:9)
  - N-O (Box-folder 17:10)
  - P-Q (Box-folder 17:11)
  - R (Box-folder 17:12)
  - S (Box-folder 17:13)
  - F-U-V (Box-folder 17:14)
  - Unemployment (Box-folder 17:15)
  - W-Z (Box-folder 17:16)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 18:1)
    [1956-1957]
  - A (Box-folder 18:2)
  - B (Box-folder 18:3)
  - C (Box-folder 18:4)
  - D (Box-folder 18:5)
  - E-J (Box-folder 18:6)
  - K-L-M (Box-folder 18:7)
  - Motor Vehicles Insurance (Box-folder 18:8)
  - N-Q (Box-folder 18:9)
  - R (Box-folder 18:10)
  - S (Box-folder 18:11)
  - T-Z (Box-folder 18:12)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 19:1)